A Guide to the Population Council records, Accession 1, RG 1 FA210
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 1, 1
  - Grant Files, 1958-1966; 2
    - Grant # I65.135
      - San Juan City Hospital, Puerto Rico: Documentation (Box 69, Folder 1257-1258)
      - San Juan City Hospital, Puerto Rico: General Correspondence and Evaluation (Box 69, Folder 1259-1260)
      - San Juan City Hospital, Puerto Rico: Narrative Reports (Box 69, Folder 1261-1262)
      - San Juan City Hospital, Puerto Rico: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 69, Folder 1263-1264)
      - San Juan City Hospital, Puerto Rico: Purchasing (Box 69, Folder 1265)
      - Kandang Kerbau Hospital, Singapore: Documentation (Box 69, Folder 1266-1267)
      - Kandang Kerbau Hospital, Singapore: General Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 1268-1270)
      - Kandang Kerbau Hospital, Singapore: Narrative Reports (Box 69, Folder 1271-1272)
      - Kandang Kerbau Hospital, Singapore: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 69, Folder 1273)
      - Kandang Kerbau Hospital, Singapore: Purchasing (Box 69, Folder 1274)
      - Thailand: General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 1275)
      - Thailand: General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 70, Folder 1276)
      - Thailand: General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 70, Folder 1277)
      - Thailand: Studies (Box 70, Folder 1278-1279)
      - Chulalongkorn Hospital, Thailand: Documentation (Box 70, Folder 1280-1281)
      - Chulalongkorn Hospital, Thailand: General Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 1282-1283)
      - Chulalongkorn Hospital, Thailand: Narrative Reports (Box 70, Folder 1284)
      - Chulalongkorn Hospital, Thailand: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 70, Folder 1285)
      - Siriraj Hospital, Thailand: Documentation (Box 70, Folder 1286)
      - Siriraj Hospital, Thailand: General Correspondence and Evaluation (Box 70, Folder 1287-1288)
      - Siriraj Hospital, Thailand: Narrative Reports (Box 70, Folder 1289)
      - Siriraj Hospital, Thailand: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 70, Folder 1290)
      - Vajira Hospital, Thailand: Documentation (Box 70, Folder 1291)
      - Vajira Hospital, Thailand: General Correspondence and Evaluation (Box 70, Folder 1292-1293)
      - Vajira Hospital, Thailand: Narrative Reports (Box 70, Folder 1294)
      - Vajira Hospital, Thailand: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 70, Folder 1295)
      - Women's Hospital, Thailand: Documentation (Box 70, Folder 1296)
      - Women's Hospital, Thailand: General Correspondence and Evaluation (Box 70, Folder 1297-1298)
      - Women's Hospital, Thailand: Narrative Reports (Box 70, Folder 1299)
      - Women's Hospital, Thailand: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 70, Folder 1300)
      - Ankara Maternity Hospital, Turkey: Documentation (Box 70, Folder 1301)
      - Ankara Maternity Hospital, Turkey: General Correspondence and Evaluation (Box 70, Folder 1302-1303)
      - Ankara Maternity Hospital, Turkey: Narrative Reports (Box 70, Folder 1304)
      - Ankara Maternity Hospital, Turkey: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 71, Folder 1305-1306)
      - Ankara Maternity Hospital, Turkey: Purchasing (Box 71, Folder 1307-1308)
      - Shatby Maternity Hospital, U.A.R.: Documentation (Box 71, Folder 1309)
      - Shatby Maternity Hospital, U.A.R.: General Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 1310-1311)
      - Shatby Maternity Hospital, U.A.R.: Narrative Reports (Box 71, Folder 1312)
      - Shatby Maternity Hospital, U.A.R.: Purchasing (Box 71, Folder 1313)
      - Cairo University, U.A.R.: Documentation (Box 71, Folder 1314-1315)
      - Cairo University, U.A.R.: General Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 1316-1317)
      - Cairo University, U.A.R.: Narrative Reports (Box 71, Folder 1318-1319)
      - Cairo University, U.A.R.: Purchasing (Box 71, Folder 1320-1321)
      - Los Angeles County General Hospital: Documentation (Box 71, Folder 1322)
      - Los Angeles County General Hospital: General Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 1323-1324)
      - Los Angeles County General Hospital: Narrative Reports (Box 71, Folder 1325)
      - Los Angeles County General Hospital: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 71, Folder 1326)
      - Los Angeles County General Hospital: Purchasing (Box 71, Folder 1327-1328)
      - Wayne County General Hospital, Michigan: Documentation (Box 71, Folder 1329-1330)
      - Wayne County General Hospital, Michigan: General Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 1331-1332)
      - Wayne County General Hospital, Michigan: Narrative Reports (Box 71, Folder 1333-1334)
      - Wayne County General Hospital, Michigan: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 71, Folder 1335-1336)
      - Harlem Hospital Center: Documentation (Box 71, Folder 1337)
      - Harlem Hospital Center: General Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 1338-1339)
      - Harlem Hospital Center: Narrative Reports (Box 71, Folder 1340-1341)
      - Harlem Hospital Center: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 71, Folder 1342)
      - Jacobi Hospital, NY: Documentation (Box 71, Folder 1343-1344)
      - Jacobi Hospital, NY: General Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 1345-1346)
      - Jacobi Hospital, NY: Narrative Reports (Box 72, Folder 1347)
      - Metropolitan Hospital, NY: Documentation (Box 72, Folder 1348-1349)
      - Metropolitan Hospital, NY: General Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 1350-1351)
      - Metropolitan Hospital, NY: Narrative Reports (Box 72, Folder 1352)
      - Metropolitan Hospital, NY: Purchasing (Box 72, Folder 1353)
      - Sloane Hospital, NY: Documentation (Box 72, Folder 1354-1355)
      - Sloane Hospital, NY: General Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 1356)
      - Sloane Hospital, NY: Narrative Reports (Box 72, Folder 1357)
      - Sloane Hospital, NY: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 72, Folder 1358)
      - Sloane Hospital, NY: Purchasing (Box 72, Folder 1359)
      - General Hospital, Washington, D.C.: Documentation (Box 72, Folder 1360-1361)
      - General Hospital, Washington, D.C.: General Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 1362-1363)
      - General Hospital, Washington, D.C.: Narrative Reports (Box 72, Folder 1364-1366)
      - Maternidad Concepcin Palacios, Venezuela: Documentation (Box 72, Folder 1367-1368)
      - Maternidad Concepcin Palacios, Venezuela: General Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 1369-1370)
      - Maternidad Concepcin Palacios, Venezuela: Narrative Reports (Box 72, Folder 1371-1372)
      - Maternidad Concepcin Palacios, Venezuela: Payments and Financial Reports (Box 73, Folder 1373-1374)
      - Maternidad Concepcin Palacios, Venezuela: Purchasing (Box 73, Folder 1375)
    - Grant # I65.136 - Columbia University, NY: Program on Instructional Materials (Box 73, Folder 1376)
    - Grant # D65.137 - Egyptian Assoc. of Population Studies: National Sample Survey of Family Planning Studies (Box 73, Folder 1377-1379)
    - Grant # D65.138 - JCRR, Taiwan: Evaluation and Training Program (Box 73, Folder 1380-1381)
    - Grant # D65.139 - U.N. - CELADE, Chile: Comparative Rural Fertility Surveys in Latin America (Box 73, Folder 1382-1383)
    - Grant # D65.140 - University of Chicago: Reduction of Birth Rates in Rural South (Box 73, Folder 1384)
    - Grant # D65.141 - University of Chicago: Family Planning Communication and Research (Box 73, Folder 1385-1386)
    - Grant # D65.142 - University of Tehran, India: Fertility Levels Studies (Box 73, Folder 1387)
    - Grant # M65.143 - Weizmann Inst. of Science, Israel: Research in Reproductive Physiology (Box 73, Folder 1388-1389)
    - Oversized Grant Material (Box 74, Folder 1390-1400)
  - National Committee on Maternal Health (NCMH), 1958-1966; 3
    Consists of two sub-series.
    Former Classification: IV 3B 04.4a-4b
    - General file, 1958-1964; 1
      Contains correspondence, memoranda, and copies or drafts of medical and demographic studies. The NCMH, under its Director of Research, Dr. Christopher Tietze, worked very closely with the Population Council, functioning as an information service for people and organizations interested in family planning and as a source of expert advice for scholars conducting demographic and medical research.
      Arranged so that large amounts of material concerning a given person, institution, or subject are stored together in one of more folders. Such material is arranged in chronological order, and the folders appear in appropriate alphabetical order throughout the General Correspondence for a given year. For each letter of the alphabet, a general folder has been used for small amounts of material filed under that letter. Material in these folders is filed alphabetically. The general folder for each letter precedes all folders that are filed under that letter and that deal with specific subjects, persons, or institutions.
      In some instances folders of correspondence of a given year contain material from previous or subsequent years. For example, a folder labeled "1959 General Correspondence / F, 1957-1959" contains material going back to 1957. The folder would appear among the 1959 general correspondence. If, then, a user of the NCMH papers is looking for 1958 correspondence with John Flynt, he or she should consult the "F" folders for both 1958 and 1959. In addition, the user should consult the "F" folders for years after 1959 if the heading on any of these folders indicates that earlier material (in this case 1958 material) is included.
      - General Correspondence, 1958
        - A, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1401)
        - B, 1955-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1402)
        - C, 1954-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1403-1404)
        - Cleveland Study - "Scientific Testing of Foam Tablets as an Effective Means of Fertility Control" - Maternal Health Association (Box 75, Folder 1405-1406)
        - D, 1955-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1407)
        - E, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1408)
        - F (Box 75, Folder 1409)
        - Fomos Tablets - Medical College of Virginia, Richmond, 1954-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1410)
        - G, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1411)
        - H, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1412-1413)
        - I, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1414)
        - International Journal of Fertility (Box 75, Folder 1415)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation (IPPF), 1956-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1416-1417)
        - J (Box 76, Folder 1418)
        - K, 1957-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1419-1420)
        - L, 1955-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1421-1422)
        - M, 1957-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1423)
        - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau - Subcommittee on the Approval of Contraceptive Material, 1958-1959 (Box 76, Folder 1424-1425)
        - N (Box 76, Folder 1426-1427)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Administrative Material (Box 76, Folder 1428-1429)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Audit Reports, 1956-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1430)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Finances (Box 76, Folder 1431)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Financial Statements (Box 76, Folder 1432)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Publications - "Recommended Procedure for the Study of the Clinical Effectiveness of Contraceptive Methods", 1958 (Box 76, Folder 1433)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Salaries and Taxes, 1958-1959 (Box 76, Folder 1434*)
        - O (Box 76, Folder 1435)
        - P, 1956-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1436)
        - R, 1957-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1437)
        - S, 1956-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1438)
        - T, 1955-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1439-1440)
        - Tietze, Christopher - Papers - "The Condom as a Contraceptive", 1958-1959 (Box 77, Folder 1441)
        - Tietze, Christopher - Papers - "Differential Fecundity and the Effectiveness of Contraception", 1958-1959 (Box 77, Folder 1442)
        - U (Box 77, Folder 1443)
        - V, 1957-1958 (Box 77, Folder 1444)
        - W, 1955-1958 (Box 77, Folder 1445)
      - General Correspondence, 1959
        - A (Box 77, Folder 1446)
        - B, 1958-1959 (Box 77, Folder 1447)
        - Barbados, 1956-1959 (Box 77, Folder 1448-1449)
        - C, 1958-1959 (Box 77, Folder 1450)
        - Cleveland Study - "Scientific Testing of Foam Tablets as an Effective Means of Fertility Control" - Maternal Health Association (Box 77, Folder 1451-1452)
        - D (Box 77, Folder 1453)
        - E (Box 77, Folder 1454)
        - F, 1958-1959 (Box 77, Folder 1455)
        - G, 1958-1959 (Box 77, Folder 1456-1457)
        - H, 1958-1959 (Box 77, Folder 1458)
        - I (Box 77, Folder 1459)
        - J (Box 77, Folder 1460)
        - K (Box 78, Folder 1461)
        - L (Box 78, Folder 1462)
        - M, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 1463)
        - N (Box 78, Folder 1464)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Administrative Material (Box 78, Folder 1465)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Finances, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 1466-1467)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Publications - "The Clinical Effectiveness of Contraceptive Methods", 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 1468)
        - O, 1957-1959 (Box 78, Folder 1469)
        - P (Box 78, Folder 1470)
        - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 1471)
        - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Clinical Testing Subcommittee, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 1472)
        - Population Council (Box 78, Folder 1473-1474)
        - R (Box 78, Folder 1475-1476)
        - T (Box 78, Folder 1477)
        - V (Box 78, Folder 1478)
        - W, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 1479)
      - General Correspondence, 1960
        - A (Box 78, Folder 1480)
        - B, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 1481-1482)
        - C (Box 78, Folder 1483)
        - Cleveland Study - "Scientific Testing of Foam Tablets as an Effective Means of Fertility Control" - Maternal Health Association (Box 78, Folder 1484)
        - Cleveland Study - "Scientific Testing of Foam Tablets as an Effective Means of Fertility Control" - Maternal Health Association (Box 79, Folder 1485*)
        - Clinical Investigation Program of Planned Parenthood Federation of America (Box 79, Folder 1486-1487)
        - Coitus Interruptus (Box 79, Folder 1488)
        - Condom (Box 79, Folder 1489)
        - Council for the Investigation of Fertility Control (CIFC), 1958-1960 (Box 79, Folder 1490)
        - D (Box 79, Folder 1491)
        - E, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 1492)
        - F (Box 79, Folder 1493)
        - G (Box 79, Folder 1494)
        - H, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 1495)
        - I (Box 79, Folder 1496)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 1497-1498)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Medical Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 1499)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Medical Committee - Field Trials Subcommittee (Box 79, Folder 1500)
        - J (Box 79, Folder 1501)
        - K, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 1502-1503)
        - L, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 1504)
        - Los Bravos Project, Puerto Rico - EMKO Cream Test, 1958-1960 (Box 79, Folder 1505)
        - M (Box 79, Folder 1506-1507)
        - Mexico Asociacin Mexicana Pro Bienestar de la Familia, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1508-1509)
        - N (Box 80, Folder 1510-1511)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Administrative Material (Box 80, Folder 1512)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Audit Reports, 1956-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1513)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Finances (Box 80, Folder 1514-1515)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Salaries and Taxes, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1516*)
        - O, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1517)
        - P, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1518)
        - Planned Parenthood Federation of America (Box 80, Folder 1519)
        - Population Association of America (Box 80, Folder 1520)
        - Population Council (Box 80, Folder 1521-1522)
        - R, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1523)
        - Rostock Meeting - International Conference on Abortion, 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 1524)
        - S (Box 80, Folder 1525)
        - Southwest Foundation for Research and Education, 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 1526-1527)
        - T (Box 80, Folder 1528)
        - U (Box 81, Folder 1529)
        - V (Box 81, Folder 1530)
        - W, 1959-1960 (Box 81, Folder 1531)
      - General Correspondence, 1961
        - A (Box 81, Folder 1532-1533)
        - B, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 1534)
        - C, 1960-1962 (Box 81, Folder 1535-1536)
        - Clearing House of the National Committee on Maternal Health (Box 81, Folder 1537)
        - Cleveland Study - "Scientific Testing of Foam Tablets as an Effective Means of Fertility Control" - Maternal Health Association (Box 81, Folder 1538-1539)
        - Clinical Investigation Program of Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 1540)
        - D (Box 82, Folder 1541)
        - E (Box 82, Folder 1542)
        - F (Box 82, Folder 1543)
        - G, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1544)
        - Graefenberg Ring, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1545-1546)
        - H, 1960-1962 (Box 82, Folder 1547-1548)
        - I, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1549)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Medical Handbook - Testing of Contraceptives, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1550)
        - J, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1551)
        - K (Box 82, Folder 1552)
        - L (Box 82, Folder 1553)
        - M (Box 82, Folder 1554-1555)
        - Menstrual Cycle Model - Statistical Evaluation of Rhythm Method (Box 82, Folder 1556)
        - Mexico - Asociacin Mexicana Pro Bienestar de la Familia - Rice-Wray, Edris (Box 82, Folder 1557)
        - N (Box 83, Folder 1558)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Administrative Material, 1960-1962 (Box 83, Folder 1559)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Finances (Box 83, Folder 1560-1561)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Publications - "Probability of a Pregnancy Resulting From a Single Unprotected Coitus", 1959-1961 (Box 83, Folder 1562)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Salaries and Taxes (Box 83, Folder 1563*)
        - New York Academy of Medicine, 1958-1961 (Box 83, Folder 1564)
        - Nomenclature Committee of the American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 1565)
        - O (Box 83, Folder 1566)
        - P (Box 83, Folder 1567)
        - Planned Parenthood Federation of America (Box 83, Folder 1568-1569)
        - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Social Research (Box 83, Folder 1570-1571)
        - Population Council, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 1572-1573)
        - Q (Box 84, Folder 1574)
        - R, 1961-1962 (Box 84, Folder 1575)
        - Rhythm Project - Lanctot, Claude, 1959-1961 (Box 84, Folder 1576)
        - Ryder Memorial Hospital Project - Humacao (Box 84, Folder 1577)
        - S (Box 84, Folder 1578-1579)
        - Southwest Foundation for Research and Education (Box 84, Folder 1580-1581)
        - T (Box 84, Folder 1582)
        - Tietze, Christopher - Papers - "The Effect of Breastfeeding on the Rate of Conception", 1959-1961 (Box 84, Folder 1583)
        - U (Box 84, Folder 1584)
        - V (Box 84, Folder 1585)
        - Vasectomy Study - Human Betterment Association, 1960-1961 (Box 84, Folder 1586-1587)
        - Vollman, R. F.- Menstrual Records (Box 84, Folder 1588)
        - W (Box 84, Folder 1589)
        - Y-Z (Box 84, Folder 1590)
      - General Correspondence, 1962
        - A, 1961-1962 (Box 84, Folder 1591)
        - B, 1961-1962 (Box 85, Folder 1592-1593)
        - C, 1961-1962 (Box 85, Folder 1594-1595)
        - Communications Project - National Committee on Maternal Health and Population Council (Box 85, Folder 1596)
        - D (Box 85, Folder 1597)
        - E (Box 85, Folder 1598-1599)
        - F (Box 85, Folder 1600)
        - Forti, Emilio - Research on New Contraceptive Method (Box 85, Folder 1601)
        - G (Box 85, Folder 1602)
        - H (Box 85, Folder 1603)
        - Hong, Sung-Bong - Paper - "Male Attitudes Toward Family Planning on the Island of Kangwha-Gum, Korea", 1961-1962 (Box 85, Folder 1604)
        - I (Box 85, Folder 1605)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation, 1961-1962 (Box 85, Folder 1606-1607)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Third Conference of the Region for Europe, the Near East and Africa (Warsaw Conference), 1961-1962 (Box 85, Folder 1608)
        - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population (IUSSP) (Box 85, Folder 1609)
        - J (Box 86, Folder 1610)
        - K, 1961-1962 (Box 86, Folder 1611-1612)
        - L, 1961-1962 (Box 86, Folder 1613)
        - M (Box 86, Folder 1614-1615)
        - Masters, William H., 1960-1962 (Box 86, Folder 1616-1617)
        - Mexico - Asociacin Mexicana Pro Bienestar de la Familia - Rice-Wray, Edris (Box 86, Folder 1618-1619)
        - N, 1961-1962 (Box 86, Folder 1620)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Administrative Material, 1962-1963 (Box 86, Folder 1621-1622)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Finances (Box 86, Folder 1623-1624)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Publications - "Pregnancy Rates and Birth Rates" (Box 86, Folder 1625)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Salaries and Taxes (Box 86, Folder 1626*)
        - O (Box 86, Folder 1627)
        - P (Box 86, Folder 1628)
        - Planned Parenthood Federation of America (Box 87, Folder 1629-1630)
        - Population Association of America (Box 87, Folder 1631-1632)
        - Population Council (Box 87, Folder 1633-1635)
        - Population Council Reprint Project (Box 87, Folder 1636)
        - R (Box 87, Folder 1637)
        - Rhythm Project, 1959-1962 (Box 87, Folder 1638)
        - S (Box 87, Folder 1639)
        - Society for the Psychological Study of Social Issues, 1961-1962 (Box 87, Folder 1640)
        - Southwest Foundation for Research and Education (Box 87, Folder 1641-1642)
        - T (Box 87, Folder 1643)
        - Thrombophlebitis Project (Box 87, Folder 1644)
        - Tietze, Christopher - Papers - "Use and Use-Effectiveness of Contraceptive Methods", 1961-1962 (Box 88, Folder 1645)
        - Tietze, Christopher and Potter, Robert - Papers - "Statistical Evaluation of the Rhythm Method", 1961-1962 (Box 88, Folder 1646)
        - U (Box 88, Folder 1647-1648)
        - V (Box 88, Folder 1649)
        - Vasectomy Study - Human Betterment Association (Box 88, Folder 1650-1651)
        - W (Box 88, Folder 1652-1653)
        - Z (Box 88, Folder 1654)
      - General Correspondence, 1963
        - A, 1962-1963 (Box 88, Folder 1655-1656)
        - Adoption Study - Rock, John, 1958-1963 (Box 88, Folder 1657-1659)
        - Adoption Study - Rock, John - Worksheets (Box 89, Folder 1660)
        - American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Conference on Fertility and Population Problems, 1962-1964 (Box 89, Folder 1661)
        - B, 1963-1964 (Box 89, Folder 1662)
        - Birth Control Manual, 1960-1964 (Box 89, Folder 1663-1664)
        - Breastfeeding, 1962-1964 (Box 89, Folder 1665)
        - C, 1962-1963 (Box 89, Folder 1666)
        - Communications Project - National Committee on Maternal Health and Population Council (Box 89, Folder 1667)
        - D (Box 89, Folder 1668)
        - E, 1962-1963 (Box 89, Folder 1669)
        - Foam Tablet Acceptability Test (Box 89, Folder 1670)
        - G (Box 89, Folder 1671)
        - H, 1934 1951 1963 (Box 89, Folder 1672-1673)
        - I, 1962-1963 (Box 89, Folder 1674)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation (Box 89, Folder 1675)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Western Hemisphere Region (Box 89, Folder 1676-1677)
        - J (Box 90, Folder 1678)
        - K (Box 90, Folder 1679-1680)
        - L, 1961-1963 (Box 90, Folder 1681)
        - M, 1962-1963 (Box 90, Folder 1682-1683)
        - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau (Box 90, Folder 1684)